[Music]
double dragon life insurance agency
we're given
the income equivalent to our efforts
[Music]
income
aside from the unlimited income
potential it provides
it also gives me the bandwidth to do
other things aside from my work
being a full-time mom as well i work on
my pro business around my daughter's
schedule
client intensive client it's just great
that i'm earning here without
compromising my health
my time and my responsibility to my
family
as a gen z i never thought that it's
possible for me to go travel abroad
i used to think that it's gonna take me
five to ten years from now
but here in double dragon it helped me
unravel that kind of opportunity
by just doing good in the business when
i first learned on my travel incentives
here came through
at first i was skeptical imagine 2017
our offering was spain oh my god
european country
but lo and behold 10 months after i got
coded i was on route to barajas
international airport in madrid that was
truly an amazing experience
[Music]
opportunities to prove and to date i was
able to qualify to 15 countries already
that includes japan usa switzerland
and many more hindi languages
a number of people it's open for
everyone and everyone could qualify
the best part of being with double
dragon
is that i get to work with mentors who
are just amazing at what they do
after world-class training here in
double dragon
come on definitely different kind of
market like corporate accounts
cold market and actually right now
indicate a legendary
[Music]
if you're going to join us here in
double dragon
indica limited source
because we are going to teach you on how
you are going to maximize
different kinds of markets it's an
acknowledgement
industry total
[Music]
and i'm fighting my big ideas approved
but one thing that i really love
is that i can help others not experience
what my friend had gone through when she
got diagnosed with cancer
sadly she was not able to survive partly
because
she was emotionally stressed because of
financial issues
when i learned about proof financial
programs
then i realized why not share it with
others
[Music]
as a nurse we take care of our patients
for today
as a financial advisor we take care of
our clients for tomorrow
as a financial advisor i help people
build
their own business as a financial
advisor i help my clients manage their
financial exposure on
life uncertainties as a financial
advisor i help my clients improve
their financial portfolio as a financial
advisor
i design and create the best program for
families
to keep them from poverty as a teacher
we lay down the foundation for tomorrow
exactly what we do as a financial
advisor in terms of our clients finances
here in this business
i am their partner in ensuring that they
will be able to achieve
their goals whatever the circumstances
will be
[Applause]
videos
[Music]
but if you will be given an opportunity
to have a career
that has high income potential a career
with a mission
a career where you can work with people
helping you
and pushing you to become a better
version of yourself to have a career
that you can work at your own pace will
you consider it
if your answer is yes then i'm inviting
you to explore this wonderful career
of becoming a financial advisor here at
double dragon
be part of our family be part of double
[Applause]
[Music]
dragon